studenttenant.com 2017-02-21

# Privacy | Student Tenant

### 1\. Privacy and Cookies Policy 

1.1 This website is operated by Jakuta Limited (a limited company registered in England; registration number 06792938; registered office The Goose Hole, Church Farm, South Harting, GU31 5QG; main trading place The Canterbury Innovation Centre, University Road, Canterbury, Kent CT2 7FG) (we, us, our). 

1.2 Capitalised words used but not defined in this Privacy and Cookies Policy will have the meanings set out in the: 

1.2.1 studenttenant.com website terms and conditions of use located at www.studenttenant.com/page/Terms (Website Terms) if you are a tenant or landlord user of the studenttenant.com website; or

1.2.2 studenttenant.com platform terms and conditions of use (Service Terms) if you are a university user. 

1.3 In this Privacy and Cookies Policy we use the word Site to mean the studenttenant.com website if you are a tenant or landlord user and the studenttenant.com platform if you are a university user.

1.4 For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act), we are the "data controller".

1.5 If you have any questions about this Privacy and Cookies Policy or any of the Website Terms or Service Terms please contact us at contact@jakuta.co.uk 

1.6 When you supply any personal information to us, we have legal obligations towards you in the way we deal with that personal information. We must collect the personal information fairly, including explaining how we will use it. This Privacy and Cookies Policy tells you when and how we will use personal information we collect from you when you use this Site. 

### 2\. Changes to the Privacy and Cookies Policy

2.1 We may revise and update this Privacy and Cookies Policy at any time and will indicate at the top of this page when this Privacy and Cookies Policy was last revised. Please periodically review the Privacy and Cookies Policy, as your continued use of this Site indicates your agreement with any changes that we make.

### 3\. We respect your privacy

3.1 The protection of your privacy in the processing of your personal information is important to us. We process any personal information we collect during your visits to this Site according to applicable data privacy and data protection legislation. 

### 4\. Collection and Usage of your personal information and acceptance

4.1 We collect certain personal information about you when you input information when using any of the functions available on this Site (for example, uploading a property to advertise it, registering your details to receive notifications about properties, or viewing usage statistics).

4.2 We may track your use of this Site by using cookies, if you consent. Please see our cookie policy located at [Insert link]. 

4.3 By submitting your personal information to this Site, by ticking appropriate boxes to indicate consent where relevant, and by using the functions on this Site, you agree that we may process your personal information in accordance with this Privacy and Cookies Policy. 

### 5\. Use and storage of your personal information

5.1 Before you are able to use some of the functionality of this Site you may need to provide your name, address, a valid email address, telephone number or any other mandatory personal information we request. There is also optional personal information you can fill in which will help to enhance your experience, however this is not mandatory. We may also require additional personal information depending on the purposes for which you use this Site.

5.2 We may use personal information we collect from you only for the purposes of:

5.2.1 hosting and administering your profile with this Site;

5.2.2 providing you with the information you request from us (such as information about properties in which you have registered an interest) and keeping a record of the information we have provided to you, including a record of ratings and comments you have provided; 

5.2.3 identifying whether you have complied with the Website Terms or Service Terms, as applicable, and otherwise for the administration and operation of this Site;

5.2.4 asking you to participate in surveys and feedback relating to this Site and for processing and analysing the results of surveys or feedback internally;

5.2.5 providing you with information about any products or services we provide that we believe may be of interest to you, but only where you have indicated your acceptance.

### 6\. Other sharing of your personal information

6.1 In addition, we may share your personal information with third parties in the following ways: 

6.1.1 we may use third parties to process personal information on our behalf (for example, we may use a third party to provide Site hosting services or to facilitate the provision of information to you or to provide products and/or services on our behalf) provided that where we do we will ensure that they have adequate security measures in place and are governed by our privacy policies in respect of the use of your personal information; 

6.1.2 we will release your personal information when we are required to do so for legal or regulatory purposes or as part of legal proceedings or where it is reasonably necessary to do so to protect our legitimate commercial interests or other users; 

6.1.3 we will release your personal information to others when you have given your consent to that release (including to third parties who wish to provide marketing or other information to you);

6.1.4 we may give personal information we hold about you to third parties as part of the process of selling our business.

### 7\. Changing or removing personal information and finding out what personal information we hold about you

7.1 You can change or remove the personal information we hold about you by logging in and editing your profile if you have one or by notifying us at contact@jakuta.co.uk 

7.2 Following receipt of your request we will endeavour to update or remove your personal information as soon as practicable, but we will not be able to do so immediately following your request.

7.3 The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. You may exercise your right at any time by contacting us at contact@jakuta.co.uk. We may apply a fee of up to £10 to deal with any such request to help meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you

### 8\. Cookies

8.1 This paragraph 8 sets out our cookie policy, explaining what cookies are, why we use cookies, what cookies we use on this Site and how to disable cookies). For more information on cookies and deletion of cookies please visit: http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies. 

8.2 Cookies are small text files. Many websites place cookies on your computer when you visit. Cookies are used to make websites work, or to make them work more efficiently, and to provide useful information to website operators. The following explains what cookies we uses on this Site and why:

Cookie Name Purpose

[Google analytics] [utma; utmb; utmc; utmz]

[These cookies collect information about how visitors use our site. We use this information to prepare reports and improve the site. This information is anonymous. The information includes the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited.

You can opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites at http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout]

[x] [x] [x]

8.3 Many web browsers allow users to control most cookies through their browser settings. More information about cookies, including details on viewing what cookies have been set and how to delete them is available at: [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)[](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

### 9\. Links to Third Party Websites

9.1 This Site may contain links to third party websites. This Privacy and Cookies Policy applies to this Site only and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of third party websites. We recommend that you read the privacy policies of those other websites if you visit them.

### 10\. Governing law and jurisdiction

  10.1 This Privacy and Cookies Policy any dispute or claim arising out of or in connection with it or its subject matter or formation (including non-contractual disputes or claims) shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the law of England. The English courts will have non-exclusive jurisdiction over any dispute or claim arising from, or related to, this Privacy and Cookies Policy

### Terms and Conditions 

<https://www.studenttenant.com/page/Terms>
